looking for affordable coverage with a
simple application
we have the solution for you for a
limited time only
introducing two easy products for you
and your loved ones
manulife easy cover and manulife easy ci
cover
you can get covered for up to a maximum
of 250
000 ringgit per life with term options
of 20 years or up to age 80.
with manulife easy cover you are
guaranteed to get the protection you
need without any medical checkup or
proof of financial documents
let's get started with basic life
protection against death
and total and permanent disability if
death is due to accidental causes
an additional 100 of the coverage amount
will be paid
and a bereavement benefit of up to 20 of
the coverage amount will be paid to your
loved ones
during this difficult time get covered
now from as low as one ringgit and 20
cent a day
for a more comprehensive coverage with
additional critical illness benefit
get manulife easy ci cover you will get
protected with manulife easy ci cover by
only answering one simple health
declaration
get all the protection under manual life
easy cover plus
five common critical illnesses cancer
stroke heart attack kidney failure and
coronary artery bypass surgery
a recovery benefit of an additional 20
of the coverage amount will be paid to
you to help ease your burdens during
your recovery
get manulife easy ci cover with
affordable premium from as low as one
ringgit and 70 cent a day
now getting coverage has never been this
easy
only available up to 31 december 2020.
find out more by calling our customer
care line
or get in touch with our professional
manulife advisor today